[Music]
[Música]
family regrettable attack on david florez
familia lamentable ataque a david flórez
antonio's son david worth it take your face
el hijo de antonio david vale la cara
off they are attacking them telling them that
quita están atacando les diciendo que
he is exercising vicarious violence
está ejerciendo violencia vicaria
brave for having had the detail the
valerosa por haber tenido el detalle el
other day at his grandmother's tribute to
otro día en el homenaje de su abuela de
have asked his aunt gloria to
haber pedido a su tía gloria que
pick the flowers for his
cogieron las flores para sus seres
loved ones even two of the people that
queridos hasta dos de las personas que
the kid remembered among whom was
el chiquillo se acordó entre los que se
olga his sister announced that she couldn't go that that
olga su hermana anunció que no pudo ir
was vicarious violence that's it
que eso era violencia de vícar ya está
you tell me what it has to do with what
ya me dirás tú qué tendrá que ver lo que
was he thinks that it comes to him that he
estaba se le ocurra que se le venga que
remembers someone vicarious violence
se acuerde de alguien violencia vicaria
because the kid doesn't even know that the
pues el chaval no sabe ni que están las
cameras are there or hasn't realized that they
cámaras ni se ha dado cuenta que sólo
were only broadcasting they are not broadcasting what
estaban emitiendo no están emitiendo que
vicarious violence but what nonsense they
violencia vicarias pero qué tonterías
talk really that they no longer know what to
hablan de verdad que ya no saben qué
invent
inventarse
really I don't know maybe people
de verdad yo no sé a lo mejor la gente
would prefer that his father's partner
preferiría que a la pareja de su padre
instead of treating him with as much
en vez de tratarlo también con tanto
love as a younger son
cariño como un hijo más chico
that they should have given us the love that he
que nos hubieran dado el amor que
received well family see you I leave you
recibió bueno familia nos vemos os dejo
here with this regrettable tweet but it
por aquí con este tweet lamentable pero
was a  Caracas stroll
era un paseíto caraquista
[Music]
[Música]